Lim Su-do
the third-year student
You shouldn't mention
that name
You're working out
to beat him, right?
How long do you think
that'll take?
Just ask Lim Su-do
to help you
take down Lee Hyeon-wu
Hyeong-ju
You're the strongest
guy in your grade
It was
worth watching you
We're third-years now
so we have to focus
on studying
You're the boss
of our school now
Do a good job
Su-do
Until then, Daemun High
was my world
The boss spot
and Hong Il-tak
were all mine
You son of a b****
Do I look
like a pushover to you?
If anyone beats him
it'll be me
Stop telling me
what to do
Get lost
I don't want Su-do
involved in this
He's known
for being cruel
Besides, I have my pride
That guy is dangerous
Should I apologize
with this?
Who knows?
Maybe he'll be moved
by my kindness
I'll just be
his errand boy
How low can I sink?
Hey, Hong Il-tak
We need to talk